saynow.com 2011-02-04

# SayNow

SayNow knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting SayNow's web site, submitting information or using any of our services, you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

### What does this privacy policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers SayNow's treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that SayNow gathers when you are accessing SayNow's web site and when you use SayNow services. The types of Personal Information collected include your full name, address, e-mail address, phone or other communication device number and other data related to your account (including contact lists and preferences). Also, this Policy covers SayNow's treatment of any Personal Information that SayNow's business partners share with SayNow. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that SayNow does not own or control, or to individuals that SayNow does not employ or manage.

### What personal information does SayNow collect?

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our customers.

### Personal information you provide to us.

We may receive and store any information you enter on our web site or in connection with our services or that you provide to us in any other way. The Personal Information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain services, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about the services.

### Personal information collected automatically.

We may receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our web site or services. SayNow may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. SayNow may also choose to automatically collect information from your use of the services, including account activity (e.g. storage use, number of log-ins), data displayed and clicked on, and other usage information (e.g. the identity of your carrier, message frequency, size of messages). SayNow only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the web site or services so that we can improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our site and services. 

### Communications

We may receive a confirmation when you open an e-mail or text message if your computer or phone or other communication device supports this type of program. We may also compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending unnecessary messages to our customers. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other communications from us, please notify us by e-mail at _optout at saynow dot com_ and include sufficient information for us to identify your account; however, please be aware that you may not be able to use the services.

### What About Cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site and on our service are visited and by how many people. SayNow cookies do not collect Personal Information, and we do not combine the general information collected through cookies with other Personal Information to tell us who you are or to identify your screen name or e-mail address. Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. 

### Will SayNow share any of the personal information it receives? 

Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only with your consent or to business partners and affiliates as described below: 

Agents: We may employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, SayNow's agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purpose.

Business Transfers: In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if SayNow, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of SayNow may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy. 

Protection of SayNow and Others: We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any law; enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of SayNow, our employees, our customers, or others.

### Is personal information about me secure?

Your SayNow Subscriber account Personal Information is protected by a pin and/or password for your privacy and security. You need to protect against unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your pin and/or password appropriately (including appropriately signing off after you have finished accessing your account).

### What personal information can I access? 

SayNow allows you to access certain information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. The types of information that you can access and update will change as our service changes. To access your information, log on to your SayNow Subscriber account.

### What choices do I have?

  * As stated previously, you can always opt not to disclose information to SayNow, even though it may be needed to take advantage of SayNow's services.
  * You may be able to add or update certain information for your account, such as those that may be listed in the "What Personal Information Can I Access" section above. When you update information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised information in our records. You may request deletion of your SayNow account by sending an e-mail to _info at saynow dot com_ and responding affirmatively to any confirmation e-mails that we may send. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.
  * If you do not wish to receive e-mail or other communications from us, please notify us by e-mail at _optout at saynow dot com_ and provide sufficient information for us to identify your account. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the SayNow web site and services, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.
  * As explained earlier, the majority of browsers allow you to monitor and restrict our use of cookies. Please note, however, that if your browser does not accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of some of our services or web site features.

### Effective date of this privacy policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 17, 2006.

### Changes to this privacy policy

SayNow may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our web site. 

### Questions or Concerns 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy at SayNow site, please send us a detailed message to _info at saynow dot com_. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
